Mss.B.J44 Mss.B.J44
American Philosophical Society
- Papers
  - Letter to [Herbert S.] Jennings, Nov. 22, 1940; 9-1/2x6; Coe, Wesley R. (Wesley Roswell), 1869-1960
    La Jolla, Cal., A.L.S. 2p.,end. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Concerning Raymond Pearl.
  - Letter to E. V. Cowdry, St.Louis, Jan. 28, 1939; 11x8-1/2; Coker, R. E. (Robert Ervin), 1876-1967
    Washington, Typed L.S. 2p. Copy sent to H.S. Jennings. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Concerning aging.
  - Letter to E. V. Cowdry, St.Louis, Feb. 7, 1939; 11x8-1/2; Coker, R. E. (Robert Ervin), 1876-1967
  - Letter to H[erbert] S. Jennings, Baltimore, Oct. 17, 1939; 11x8-1/2; Coker, R. E. (Robert Ervin), 1876-1967
    Washington, Typed L.S. 1p.,end. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Is on committee on biological processes of aging.
  - Letter to [Herbert S.] Jennings, May 4, 1940; 11x8-1/2; Coker, R. E. (Robert Ervin), 1876-1967
    Typed L.S. 1p. Copy. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Meeting is postponed.
  - Letter to [Herbert S.] Jennings, June 10, 1940; 11x8-1/2; College of the City of New York (1926-1961)
    Typed L. 2p. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) filed under: Salkins, G.N. Concerning publications.
  - Letter to H[erbert] S. Jennings, Baltimore, Dec. 17, 1921; 11x8-1/2; Collins, Hamer H
    Pittsburgh, A.L.S 1p.,end. (see H.S. Jennings papers Asks information pertaining to the anatomy of the cat.
  - Letter to [Herbert S.] Jennings, Dec. 4, 1923; 6-1/4x8; Colton, Harold Sellers, 1881-1970
    Philadelphia, A.L.S. 1p.,end. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Invites him to visit with them.
  - Letter to [Herbert S. Jennings], Dec. 18, 1939; 11x8-1/2; Columbia University
    New York, Typed L. 1p.,end. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Concerning a publication.
  - Letter to H[erbert] S. Jennings, Baltimore, April 15, 1924; 11x8-1/2; Columbia University. Press
    New York, Printed L.filled in in ms. 1p. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Business.
  - Letter to H[erbert] S. Jennings, Baltimore, June 4, 1924; 11x8-1/2; Columbia University. Press
    New York, Typed L.S.: A[lfred] Hartog. 1p.,end. (see H.S.Jennings papers.) Business.
  - Letter to Herbert S. Jennings, Feb. 9, 1932; 11x8-1/2; Columbia University. Press
    New York, Typed L. 1p.,end. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Concerning the reprint of his work: Behavior of the lower organisms.
  - Letter to H[erbert] S. Jennings, Dec. 2, 1939; 10-1/2x8; Columbia University. Press
    New York, L. 1p.,end. (see H.S.Jennings papers.) Asks if T.N.Jenkins can quote from his publication.
  - Letter to H.S. Jennings, Dec. 4, 1940; 10-1/2x8 and 11x8-1/2; Columbia University. Press
    New York, Typed L. 1p.and enc.of 6p. (see H.S.Jennings papers.) M.R.Brunstetter wishes to quote from a publication.
  - Letter to H[erbert] S. Jennings, April 17, 1942; 10-1/2x8, 11x8-1/2; Columbia University. Press
    New York, L. 1p.and enc. of 1p. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Tracy I. Storer wishes to reproduce material from his publication.
  - Statement of account with Herbert S. Jennings, 1919-1920; 11x8-1/2; Columbia University. Press
    Printed D.filled in with type. 2p. (see H.S. Jennings papers.)
  - Letter to H[erbert] S. Jennings, Baltimore, Dec. 1, 1933; 11x8-1/2; Conklin, Edwin Grant, 1863-1952
    Princeton, Typed L.S. 1p. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Friendly letter.
  - Letter to H[erbert] S. Jennings, Los Angeles, May 27, 1941; 11x8-1/2; Conklin, Edwin Grant, 1863-1952
    Philadelphia, Typed L.S. 1p.,end. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Concerning his article which the APS will publish in the Proceedings.
  - Review of H.S. Jenning's publication, 1930; 11x8-1/2; Conklin, Edwin Grant, 1863-1952
    Typed D.S.with initials. 3p.,end. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Printed: Scientific Book Club Review, vol.1, no. 4, p. 42.
  - Letter to [Herbert S.] Jennings, Jan. 24, 1924; 11x8-1/2; Coryier, W J
    Rutgers, A.L.S. 1p.,end. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Thanks for publications.
  - Letter to [Herbert S. Jennings], Jan. 9, 1939; 11x8-1/2; Cowdry, E. V. (Edmund Vincent), 1888-1975
    St. Louis, Mimeographed L.S. 1p. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Concerning aging.
  - Letter to H[erbert] S. Jennings, Los Angeles, Feb. 15, 1939; 11x8-1/2; Cowdry, E. V. (Edmund Vincent), 1888-1975
    Typed L.S. 1p. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Concerning the study of aging.
  - Letter to H[erbert] S. Jennings, Baltimore, April 19, 1941; 11x8-1/2; Cowdry, E. V. (Edmund Vincent), 1888-1975
    St.Louis, Typed L.S. 1p.,end. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Concerning a publication on ageing.
  - Letter to H[erbert] S. Jennings, Los Angeles, May 2, 1941; 11x8-1/2; Cowdry, E. V. (Edmund Vincent), 1888-1975
    St.Louis, Typed L.S. 1p. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) concerning an article on ageing.
  - Letter to H[erbert] S. Jennings, Baltimore, July 17, 1941; 11x8-1/2; Cowdry, E. V. (Edmund Vincent), 1888-1975
    Typed L.S. 1p. and enc. of 2p. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Concerning the revision of a publication.
  - Letter to H[erbert] S. Jennings. Los Angeles, Aug. 11, 1941; 11x8-1/2; Cowdry, E. V. (Edmund Vincent), 1888-1975
    St. Louis, Typed L.S. 1p.,end. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Business.
  - Letter to [Herbert S. Jennings], Nov. 21, 1938; 11x8-1/2; Cowdry, Edmund V. (Edmund Vincent), 1888-1975
    Typed L. 1p. Copy. Enc. of 4 leaves. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Concerning aging.
  - Letter to [Herbert S. Jennings], Dec. 2, 1938; 11x8-1/2; Cowdry, Edmund V. (Edmund Vincent), 1888-1975
    St. Louis, Typed L. 1p.,end. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Wishes to hold a committee meeting.
  - Letter to [Herbert S.] Jennings, Feb. 5, 1918; 6-3/4x5; Cowles, Rheinart Parker, 1872-
    Manila, A.L.S. 5p. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Friendly letter.
  - Letter to [Herbert S.] Jennings, June 29, 1918; 9-1/2x6; Cowles, Rheinart Parker, 1872-
    Baltimore, A.L.S. 1p. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Friendly letter.
  - Letter to [Herbert S.] Jennings, April 22, 1919; 10-1/2x8; Cowles, Rheinart Parker, 1872-
    Manila, A.L.S. 3p. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Friendly letter.
  - Letter to [Herbert S.] Jennings, May 13, 1919; 10-1/2x8; Cowles, Rheinart Parker, 1872-
    Manila, A.L.S. 2p. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Friendly letter.
  - Letter to H[erbert] S. Jennings, Baltimore, Feb. 2, 1933; 8x5; Cross, Wilbur Lucius, 1862-1948
    New Haven, Typed L.S. 1p. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Concerning his publication.
  - Letter to [Herbert S.] Jennings, Feb. 8, 1924; 8x5; Cutler, D. Ward (Donald Ward)
    A.L.S. 1pp,end. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Thanks for publication.
  - Letter to Herbert S. Jennings, Los Angeles, June 14, 1939; 11x8-1/2; Danforth, Charles H. (Charles Haskell), b. 1883
  - Letter to H[erbert] S. Jennings, Baltimore, Aug. 27, 1924; 11x8-1/2; Daniels, Dorothy Loomis, 1894-
    Princeton, Typed L.S. 1p. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Asks question.
  - Letter to H[erbert] S. Jennings, Baltimore, Sept. 25, 1924; 11x8-1/2; Daniels, Dorothy Loomis, 1894-
    Princeton, Typed L.S. 1p. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Business.
  - Letter to [Herbert S.] Jennings, March 7, 1924; 10x8; Dart, Raymond A. (Raymond Arthur), 1893-
    Johannesburg, A.L.S. 2P.,end. (see H. S. Jennings papers.) Friendly letter. Thanks for publications.
  - Letter to H[erbert] S. Jennings, Baltimore, Oct. 30, 1924; 7x6; Davenport, Charles Benedict, 1866-1944
    Long Island, A.L.S. 1p. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Congratulates him on a paper.
  - Letter to [Herbert S.] Jennings, June 6, 1921; 11x8-1/2; Davis, Bradley M. (Bradley Moore), b. 1871
    Ann Arbor, Typed L.S. 1p. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Concerning a scientific meeting.
  - Letter to [Herbert S.] Jennings, June 28, 1921; 11x8-1/2; Davis, Bradley M. (Bradley Moore), b. 1871
    Ann Arbor, A.L.S. 1p. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Concerning a scientific meeting.
  - Letter to [Herbert S.] Jennings, Aug. 5, 1921; 11x8-1/2; Davis, Bradley M. (Bradley Moore), b. 1871
  - Letter to [Herbert S.] Jennings, Aug. 10, 1921; 11x8-1/2; Davis, Bradley M. (Bradley Moore), b. 1871
    Ann Arbor, A.L.S. 1p. (see H. S. Jennings papers.) Concerning a scientific meeting.
  - Letter to [Herbert S.] Jennings, Aug. 27, 1921; 11x8-1/2; Davis, Bradley M. (Bradley Moore), b. 1871
    Ann Arbor, Typed L.S. 1p. (see H. S. Jennings papers.) Concerning a meeting.
  - Letter to [Herbert S.] Jennings, Sept. 21, 1921; 11x8-1/2; Davis, Bradley M. (Bradley Moore), b. 1871
    Ann Arbor, A.L.S. 2p. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Concerning the organization of a proposed meeting.
  - Letter to [Herbert S.] Jennings, Sept. 29, 1921; 11x8-1/2; Davis, Bradley M. (Bradley Moore), b. 1871
    Ann Arbor, A.L.S. 1p. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Friendly letter.
  - Letter to [Herbert S.] Jennings, Oct. 5, 1921; 7x8; Davis, Bradley M. (Bradley Moore), b. 1871
    Ann Arbon, A.L.S. 1p. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Concerning a publication.
  - Letter to [Herbert S.] Jennings, Nov. 7, 1921; 11x8-1/2; Davis, Bradley M. (Bradley Moore), b. 1871
    Ann Arbon, Typed L.S. 1p.,end. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Concerning a publication.
  - Letter to Herbert S. Jennings, Baltimore, Feb. 21, 1940; 10-1/2x8; Davis, Christine M
    New York, Typed L.S. 1p.,end. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Requests reprint of an article.
  - Letter to H[erbert] S. Jennings, Oct. 30, 1934; 8-1/2x5-1/2; De Garis, Charles F
    Baltimore, Typed L.S. 1p. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Forwards prints to be included in his paper on Heritable effects of conjugation ...of paramecium. (see No.62 of H.S.Jennings papers for these prints and the papers.)
  - Letter to H[erbert] S. Jennings, Baltimore, Jan. 17, 1924; 11x8-1/2; Detlefsen, John Adolph, 1883-
    Philadelphia, Typed L.S. 1p. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Concerning Kammerer.
  - Letter to H[erbert] S. Jennings, Baltimore, Jan. 28, 1924; 11x8-1/2; Detlefsen, John Adolph, 1883-
    Philadelphia, Typed L.S. 1p.,end. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Concerning genetics.
  - Letter to H[erbert] S. Jennings, Los Angeles, Dec. 2, 1940; 11x8-1/2; Domm, Lincoln Valentine, 1896-
    Chicago, Typed L.S. 1p.,end. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Has received the memoir on Raymond Pearl.
  - Letter to H[erbert] S. Jennings, Los Angeles, Jan. 24, 1941; 11x8-1/2; Domm, Lincoln Valentine, 1896-
    Chicago, Typed L.S. 1p.,end. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Concerning the death of Dr.Pearl.
  - Letter to [Herbert S.] Jennings, Nov. 11, 1924; 10-1/2x8; Duerden, J. E. (James Edwin), 1869-1937
    Grahamstown, S. Africa, A.L.S. 1p. (see H. S. Jennings papers.) Thanks for reprints.
  - Letter to H[erbert] S. Jennings, Baltimore, Dec. 16, 1923; 5-1/2x8-1/2; Dummer, Ethel Sturges
    Chicago, Typed L.S. 1p.,end. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Compliments him on his article on immigration.
  - Letter to Herbert S. Jennings, Baltimore, Feb. 24, 1931; 11x8-1/2; Dummer, Ethel Sturges
    Chicago, Typed L.S. 1p.,end.and enc.of 1p. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Concerning their publication on progressive education.
  - Letter to [Herbert S.] Jennings, Dec. 3, 1945; 5-1/2x8-1/2; Dummer, Ethel Sturges
    Chicago, Typed L.S. 1p.,end. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Concerning their publication on education.
  - Letter to Herbert Spencer, Jennings, Los Angeles, Dec. 19, 1940; 11x8-1/2; Dunshee, Earl
    Los Angeles, Typed L.S. 5p. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Friendly letter.
  - Letter to H[erbert] S. Jennings, Baltimore, Nov. 18, 1933; 11x8-1/2; East, Edward M. (Edward Murray), 1878-1938
    Boston, Typed L.S. 1p. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Asks question concerning genetics.
  - Letter to [Herbert S.] Jennings, Nov. 27, 1933; 11x8-1/2; East, Edward M. (Edward Murray), 1878-1938
    Boston, A.L.S. 1p. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Concerning an article on genetics.
  - Letter to H[erbert] S. Jennings, Baltimore, Dec. 4, 1933; 8-1/2x5-1/2; East, Edward M. (Edward Murray), 1878-1938
  - Letter to [Herbert S.] Jennings, April 19, [1927?]; 11x8-1/2; Eaton, G. D. (Geoffrey Dell), 1894-1930
    New York, Typed L.S. 1p. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Asks for an article from him.
  - Letter to [Herbert S.] Jennings, August 9, [1927?]; 10-1/2x6-1/2; Eaton, G. D. (Geoffrey Dell), 1894-1930
    New York, Typed L.S. 1p. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Friendly letter.
  - Letter to [Herbert S.] Jennings, Aug. 23, [1927]; 10-1/2x8-1/2; Eaton, G. D. (Geoffrey Dell), 1894-1930
    New York, Typed L.S. 1p. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Concerning an article for Plain talk.
  - Letter to H[erbert] S. Jennings, Baltimore, Oct. 29, 1927; 10-1/2x6-1/2; Eaton, G. D. (Geoffrey Dell), 1894-1930
    New York, Typed L.S. 1p. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Concerning an article on eugenics.
  - Letter to H[erbert] S. Jennings, Baltimore, Nov. 1, 1927; 10-1/2x6-1/2; Eaton, G. D. (Geoffrey Dell), 1894-1930
    New York, Typed L.S. 1p. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Concerning an article on genetics.
  - Letter to H[erbert] S. Jennings, Baltimore, Dec. 29, 1927; 10-1/2x6-1/2; Eaton, G. D. (Geoffrey Dell), 1894-1930
    New York, Typed L.S. 1p. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Has been ill and cannot judge articles.
  - Letter to H[erbert] S. Jennings, Baltimore, Jan. 4, 1928; 10-1/2x6-1/2; Eaton, G. D. (Geoffrey Dell), 1894-1930
    New York, Typed L.S. 1p. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Concerning an article for publication.
  - Letter to H[erbert] S. Jennings, Baltimore, Jan. 6, 1928; 10-1/2x6-1/2; Eaton, G. D. (Geoffrey Dell), 1894-1930
    New York, Typed L.S. 1p. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Concerning an article.
  - Letter to H[erbert] S. Jennings, Baltimore, Jan. 10, 1928; 10-1/2x6-1/2; Eaton, G. D. (Geoffrey Dell), 1894-1930
  - Letter to [Herbert S.] Jennings, Aug. 22, 1932; 7-3/4x5-1/2; Edwards, Arthur
    Buffalo, A.L.S. 4p.,end. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Friendly letter on his book on genetics
  - Letter to H[erbert] S. Jennings, Los Angeles, Dec. 14, 1940; 11x8-1/2; Emerson, Alfred Edwards, 1896-
    Chicago, Typed L.S. 1p. (see H. S. Jennings papers.) Scientific studies.
  - Letter to H[erbert] S. Jennings, Baltimore, Feb. 8, 1931; 11x8-1/2; Eshleman, Cyrus H
    Ludington, Mich., Typed L.S. 1p. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Concerning eugenics.
  - Letter to H[erbert] S. Jennings, Los Angeles, Nov. 30, 1941; 3-1/4x5-1/2; Eshleman, Cyrus H
    Cleveland, O., A.L.S.on postal card. 1p.and add.,end. (see H.S. Jennings papers) Concerning amalgamation of races.
  - Letter to [Herbert S.] Jennings, April 9, 1930; 10x8; Faber and Faber
    London A.L.S.: F.V. Morley. 1p. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Concerning his publication.
  - Letter to H[erbert] A.[sic] Jennings, Baltimore, Dec. 15, 1930; 10x7-1/2; Faber and Faber
    London, Typed L. 1p. Enc. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Forwards letter. For enclosure, see letter from W.J.Rasbridge to Faber & Fater; Dec.10,1930.
  - Letter to [Herbert S.] Jennings, Oct. 23, 1933; Fairchild, Milton
    Washington, A.L.S. 4p.,end.and enc.of 2p. Various sizes. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Friendly letter about his latest publication.
  - Letter to H[erbert] S. Jennings, Baltimore, Jan. 1, 1934; 11x8-1/2; Fletcher, Henry F. (Henry Frederick), 1871-1937
    Hazardville, Conn., A.L.S. 1p. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Friendly letter.
  - Letter to H[erbert] S. Jennings, Baltimore, Philadelphia, Feb. 20, 1924; 11x8-1/2; Fox, William J., 1897-
    Typed L.S. 1p. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Concerning reprints from an article. on Leidy.
  - Letter to Herbert S. Jennings, Baltimore, Feb. 26, 1924; 11x8-1/2; Fox, William J., 1897-
    Philadelphia, Typed L.S. 1p.,end. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Concerning a publication on Leidy.
  - Letter to H[erbert] S. Jennings. Baltimore, May 25, 1939; 10x8; Fraenkel, Gottfried Samuel, 1901-
    London, Typed L.S. 1p.,end. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Asks permission to reproduce some illustrations which he has published.
  - Letter to H[erbert] S. Jennings, Pasadena, Cal., April 6, 1940; 10-1/2x7-1/4; Free, Emons S
  - Letter to H[erbert] S. Jennings, Los Angeles, Dec. 29, 1940; 11x8-1/2; Funderburk, W H, jr.
    A.L.S. 1p.,end. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Asks for reprint.
  - Letter to [Herbert S.] Jennings, Dec. 18, 1940; 11x8-1/2; Gates, R. Ruggles (Reginald Ruggles), 1882-1962
    Berkeley, A.L.S. 1p.,end. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Concerning his lecture delivered at the U of P bicentennial celebration.
  - Letter to Herbert Spencer Jennings, Los Angeles, June 29, 1939; 11x8-1/2; Gates, Thomas Sovereign, 1873-
    Philadelphia, Typed L.S. 1p. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Concerning the U of P bicentenniel cellebration.
  - Letter to Herbert Spencer Jennings, Los Angeles, July 24, 1939; 11x8-1/2; Gates, Thomas Sovereign, 1873-
    Philadelphia, Typed L.S. 1p. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Friendly letter.
  - Letter to Herbert Spencer Jennings, Los Angeles, Oct. 4, 1940; 11x8-1/2; Gates, Thomas Sovereign, 1873-
    Philadelphia, Typed L.S. 1p. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Thanks for his activities during the U of P bicentennial celebration.
  - Letter to [Herbert S.] Jennings, Nov. 21, 1940; 11x8-1/2; Gauze, G. F. (Georgiĭ Frantsevich), 1910-1986
    A.L.S. 1p. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Forwards manuscript for publication. For manuscript, see: J.F. Gause. The effect of natural selection...; 1940. H.S.Jennings papers, no. 85.
  - Letter to H[erbert] S. Jennings, Baltimore, March 3, 1925; 5x6-1/2; Gehr, Frances
    Pittsburgh, A.L.S. 2p. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Asks for reprints of an article.
  - Letter to H[erbert] S. Jennings, Baltimore, Nov. 17, 1938; 11x8-1/2; Genetics
    New York, Typed L.S.: L.C. Dunn. 1p (see H.S. Jennings. papers.) Will be glad to publish his article.
  - Letter to H[erbert] S. Jennings, Baltimore, Dec. 2, 1938; 11x8-1/2; Genetics
    New York, Typed L.S.: Dorothy Davis. 1p. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Concerning his article.
  - Letter to H[erbert] S. Jennings, Dec. 22, 1938; 11x8-1/2; Genetics
    Baltimore; New York, Typed L.S.: Dorothy Davis. 1p. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Concerning his publication.
  - Letter to H[erbert] S. Jennings, Baltimore, Jan. 5, 1939; 11x8-1/2; Genetics
    New York, Typed L.S.: Dorothy Davis. 1p. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Concerning an article.
  - Letter to H[erbert] S. Jennings, Los Angeles, April 3, 1939; 3-1/4x5-1/2; Genetics
    New York, Typed L.S.: Dorothy Davis, on postal card. 1p.,end.and add. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Asks for any possible corrections.
  - Letter to H[erbert] S. Jennings, Los Angeles, Nov. 30, 1940; 11x8-1/2; Genetics
    New York, Typed L.S.: M.M.Rhoades. 1p.,end. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Asks him to prepare biographical sketch of Raymond Pearl.
  - Letter to H[erbert] S. Jennings, Los Angeles, Dec. 7, 1940; 11x8-1/2; Genetics
    New York, Typed L.S.: M.M. Rhoades. 1p. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Concerning a biographical sketch of Raymond Pearl.
  - Letter to H[erbert] S. Jennings, Los Angeles, Dec. 20, 1940; 11x8-1/2; Genetics
    New York, Typed L.S.: M.M.Rhoades. 1p.,end. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Thanks for biographical sketch of Raymond Pearl. (Sketch of Pearl, in galley proof form is enclosed.)
  - Letter to H[erbert] S. Jennings, Los Angeles, Jan. 18, 1941; 3-1/4x5-1/2; Genetics
    New York, A.L.S.: M.M.Rhoades on postal card. 1p.and add. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Concerning the biographical sketch of Raymond Pearl.
  - Letter to H[erbert] S. Jennings, Los Angeles, Aug. 1, 1941; 11x8-1/2; Genetics
    New York, Typed L.S.: Olive M. Brown. 1p.and enc.of 2p. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Concerning his article for publication and suggestions for it.
  - Letter to [Herbert S.] Jennings, Jan. 26, 1942; 8-1/2x5-1/2; Gerould, John Hiram, 1868-1961
    Hanover, N.H., A.L.S. 1p., end. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Thanks for reprints.
  - Letter to H[erbert] S. Jennings, Baltimore, Aug. 12, 1938; 11x8-1/2; Giese, Arthur Charles, 1904-1994
    Typed L.S. 1p. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Would like to present a paper.
  - Letter to H[erbert] S. Jennings, Baltimore, Aug. 22, 1938; 11x8-1/2; Giese, Arthur Charles, 1904-1994
    A.L.S. 1p.,end. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Concerning the paper he will read.
  - Letter to [Herbert S.] Jennings, Sept. 14, 1938; 11x8-1/2; Giese, Arthur Charles, 1904-1994
    A.L.S. 1p. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Concerning a paper which he will read.
  - Letter to H[erbert] S. Jennings, Baltimore, Oct. 5, 1938; 11x8-1/2; Giese, Arthur Charles, 1904-1994
  - Letter to H[erbert] S. Jennings, Baltimore, Oct. 31, 1938; 11x8-1/2; Giese, Arthur Charles, 1904-1994
    Typed L.S. 1p. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Concerning an article to be published.
  - Letter to H[erbert] S. Jennings, Los Angeles, Jan. 25, 1939; 11x8-1/2; Giese, Arthur Charles, 1904-1994
    Typed L.S. 1p. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Will send article for publication.
  - Letter to [Herbert S.] Jennings, Jan. 26, 1939; 11x8-1/2; Giese, Arthur Charles, 1904-1994
    A.L.S. 1p. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Will send paper for publication.
  - Letter to H[erbert] S. Jennings, Baltimore, Oct. 10, 1933; 11x8-1/2; Gill, John D
    Philadelphia, Typed L.S. 1p.and enc. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Forwards newspaper clipping in which he might be interested.
  - Letter to H[erbert] S. Jennings, May 6, 1931; 10x7-1/4; Gini, Corrado, 1884-1965
    Rome, Typed L.S. 1p., end. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Presents publication which reviews one of his works.
  - Letter to Herbert S. Jennings, Baltimore, May 4, 1925; 10-3/4x7-1/4; Goldsmith, William Marion, 1888-
    Winfield, Kans., Typed L.S. 1p. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Asks for reprint of an article.
  - Letter to [Herbert S.] Jennings, Jan. 28, [1924]; 4-1/2x7; Goodrich, Edwin S. (Edwin Stephen), 1868-1946
    Oxford, Eng., A.L.S. 1p. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Asks permission to reproduce from a publication.
  - Letter to H[erbert] S. Jennings, Los Angeles, Dec. 28, 1940; 9x6; Green, Edward Hadley, 1906-
    New York, A.L.S. 1p., end. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Asks for reprint.
  - Letter to [Herbert S.] Jennings, Nov. 12, 1930; 11x8-1/2; Grier, Norman MacDowell, 1890-
    A.L.S. 1p.and newspaper clipping. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Encloses review of Jennings's book.
  - Letter to H[erbert] S. Jennings, Los Angeles, July 15, 1940; 11x8-1/2; Griggs, Robert F. (Robert Fiske), b. 1881
    Washington, Typed L.S. 1p.,end. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Committee on ageing is reduced.
  - Letter to H[erbert] S. Jennings, Baltimore, Nov. 1, 1933; 6-1/2x6; Griswold, Benjamin Howell, Jr.
  - Letter to [Herbert S.] Jennings, Dec. 17, 1940; 11x8-1/2; Gudger, E. W. (Eugene Willis), 1866-1956
    New York, A.L.S. 1p. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Friendly letter.
  - Letter to Herbert [S.] Jennings, Baltimore, Jan. 11, 1940; 11x8-1/2; Gutteridge, Mary Valentine, 1887-
    New York, Typed L.S. 1p.,end. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Asks permission to quote from one of his books.
  - Letter to H[erbert] S. Jennings, Baltimore, March 13, 1933; 11x8-1/2; Hanson, A W
    Chicago, Typed L.S. 1p. (see H.S. Jennings Papers.) Praises his publication.
  - Letter to H[erbert] S. Jennings, Baltimore, Oct. 1, 1924; 3-1/4x5-1/2; Hargett, C W
    A.L.S.on postal card. 1p.and add. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Thanks for reprints.
  - Letter to H[erbert] S. Jennings, Baltimore, Sept. 23, 1933; 11x8-1/2; Harrison, Ross G. (Ross Granville), 1870-1959
    New Haven, Typed L.S. 1p. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Thanks for publication.
  - Diploma to Herbertum Spencer Jennings, June 26, 1895; 15x19-1/2; Harvard University
    D.S.: Carolus-Guil. Eliot, pres. and Carolus Franklin Dunbar, decanus. 1p. In Latin Parchment. (see H.S. Jennings papers.)
  - Diploma to Herbertus Spencer Jennings, June 24, 1896; 15x19; Harvard University
    Cambridge, D.S.: Carolus. Guil. Eliot, pres. and Jacobus Mills Peirce, Decanus. 1p. In Latin. Parchment. (see H.S. Jennings papers.)
  - Letter to H[erbert] S. Jennings, Nov. 5, 1920; 6-3/4x5-1/4; Harwood, H H
    Richmond, Va., A.L.S. 1p.,end. (see H.S.Jennings papers.) Wishes to purchase his "Life and death...in unicellular organisms."
  - Letter to H[erbert] S. Jennings, Baltimore, Dec. 3, 1930; 11x8-1/2; Hazlitt, Henry, 1894-1993